(Episode 4)
Ms. Choi, please.
Hold on. Just hear me out.
Hello?
Ms. Choi.
Did you meet your first love
in your hometown yesterday?
What is your real name?
What is the name of your first love?
Tree.
Eun Seo. Choi Eun Seo.
You look beautiful.
Jun Seo, come this way, too.
Congratulations. I can't believe
you have grown up to get married.
He is gorgeous.
Isn't there a reward for me today?
I do have something for you.
But please wait until the party is over.
When is the party over?
Are we not done yet?
No way. We still have so much to do.
We'll drop our parents off at home first,
have dinner with our cousins,
and also send thank you cards out
to the guests who came today.
I can't do that.
Let's get out of here.
You there.
Yes, sir.
How dare you look straight into my eyes!
What? Do you have two children? You?
Yes, sir.
I said I have two children,
but didn't say they were my children.
You.
Yes, sir.
You said you were 37 years old,
didn't you?
Yes, I did.
What?
You always flirt with women, so...
I got worried,
and told you I was 37 years old.
Is there a problem?
I do not think you can blame me.
If I had told you I was 22 years old,
would you have left me alone?
We are not allowed to have chats
with guests during work.
Have a good day.
By the way,
it has been fun and intriguing
to observe your complicated relationships.
But women do not like that.
That.
These pants don't even have a zipper.
Is it bright? Is the light bright enough?
Is it for my solo exhibition?
You said you would move
to a new work studio.
You can work here.
This is your prize and my engagement gift.
Is this your engagement gift?
It was not that easy
to move everything here alone.
That was why I didn't say anything
about you going to your hometown.
Why did you move my stuff without asking?
Are you upset?
No, I am not, but...
This is too much to take as a gift.
You needn't feel that way.
This place has been empty
since I bought it.
You can work here...
and it would be our temporary home
until the wedding.
But still, who gives a house
as an engagement gift?
Besides, I am going to Sokcho soon.
Do you remember Ji Hwan in Sokcho?
He rented an abandoned school.
So, I will help with his work there,
and I will also teach classes
at a university nearby.
You should've told me.
You should've told me before you did this.
It must've been a lot of work
to move everything.
What a waste.
Ms. Choi, please.
Yes, sir. I will connect you with her.
Hello?
You know that.
You know what types of girls I'm into.
You know I have pretty high standards.
I'm not a Casanova who goes for any girl.
What are you doing?
Ms. Choi? No way!
She is not even close to my type.
My types are...
Catherine Zeta-Jones when the girl
is sitting down,
Claudia Schiffer when the girl
is standing up.
But, she is very short...
and looks like an old lady.
But, she said she was 22 years old.
That can't be true. That is a lie.
That is an absolute lie.
Han Tae Seok. What are you talking about?
Why did you call me and talk about a girl?
Don't you even want to hear about me?
- About what?
- My engagement party.
Don't you want to know how it went?
- What are you doing?
- Right.
Yoon Jun Seo.
Okay, congratulations.
Thank you.
I am coming soon. See you then.
Yes, this is the operator.
My engagement party.
An engagement party? Is he a friend?
How is my father?
Yes, he is well.
His wife's birthday is next week.
You are coming, right?
Would they be pleased if I did?
Give it to me. Where do I need to sign?
Right here, please.
It's a regular personnel realignment
held every three months.
What is a personal maid?
Well.
It is a service for VIP guests...
Do you need a personal maid?
What is this?
How come an operator switches
to a maid so suddenly?
How could this happen?
Have you heard that the youngest son
of the CEO is staying here?
Then, is he...
The troublemaker whom the president
and the CEO have given up on.
Just give him whatever he wants.
He is also a womanizer, so...
the reason he specifically
chose this girl is...
Are you saying the girl has issues?
Who knows? They might like each other...
When did he have time to seduce her?
I was so nervous because I didn't expect
we'd be in the same department.
I was surprised when you walked in.
- Didn't you recognize me?
- No, I didn't.
How lucky to get in the same department?
Choi Eun Seo?
I am Manager Kim Moon Jung.
I will manage and supervise
your work from now on,
so please discuss any issues,
even trivial ones, with me.
Since housekeeping is the job...
that serves guests in the closest way,
your sincerity will determine
the impression of our hotel.
Always pay attention to the guests.
However, personal relationships
with guests are never allowed.
You will be fired no matter what,
under the company policy.
Do you understand, Choi Eun Seo?
A personal maid? What is this all about?
Don't pretend you can't hear me.
This pool has an audio system underwater.
I am an operator, not even
a full-time employee at this hotel.
What do people think about this?
My manager already has
a bad impression of me.
I will be fired if people think
I am in a relationship with the guest.
Will you take responsibility
if that happens?
Will you take responsibility?
Take responsibility? How would I do that?
How would I do that?
I apologize, sir.
For a moment, I thought we could talk.
I overestimated you.
Having a conversation is only possible
between humans.
What?
Get prepared for it.
I will call room services days and nights.
So you had better get ready.
Jun Seo, I heard when you were in Korea...
you used to draw a lot of portraits
in middle school.
But why haven't you painted me?
You are too beautiful.
You are too beautiful for me to paint.
What is it?
Yes?
This is a place near the school
where I am going to stay.
So it is close to your hometown.
Did you use to go there often
when you were young?
No, just once with my sister.
Did you go with Sin Ae?
No, I didn't go with her.
I went there with my cousin.
Your cousin?
What did you do?
We just hung out.
I drew her face here this big,
and we just hung out.
She was probably not as pretty as I am,
so you drew her.
No, she was not.
What is she doing now?
What?
I lost contact with her
since leaving for the U.S.
I have been looking for her
since I came back last year.
I heard she moved to Seoul.
You said she was your cousin.
She is a distant relative.
I will go to Sokcho again next week
before the move.
I will also stop by the school.
I will go with you. I miss Tae Seok, too.
You can come next time when I am moving.
Tae Seok will come to Seoul that day
for his mother's birthday.
By the way, he is being more patient
than we thought.
Ms. Choi, I am hungry.
You have three minutes, okay?
I will time you.
What is this?
Did you want to see me?
Did you lose something?
Yes. I lost my watch.
I am going to Seoul this evening
for my mother's birthday.
Have you seen my watch here?
It was there.
Did you really see it here?
When I was cleaning out the trash...
Is it with trash?
How could you make such a mistake?
I can't believe it.
What are we doing here?
What is wrong with me?
Why do I have so much bad luck?
I had enough trouble
with a watch a long time ago.
Eun Seo.
No. I didn't do it.
I didn't.
It's not here.
When do we dig up all of them?
I could not find your watch. I am sorry.
For now, please take this
for your convenience.
I am not sure how much your watch costs...
About 2,400 dollars?
Or 3,200 dollars?
Did you say 2,400 dollars
or 3,200 dollars?
But, what can we do here?
You found your watch!
You actually found it!
So was that...?
Thanks for the great pizza.
That was a joke, of course.
Was it a joke?
Are you saying that was a joke?
I had to dig up all the trash
at the dumpsite to look for it.
And you're saying it was a joke?
People like you...
I hate people like you so much.
I am sorry, sir. Excuse me for now.
Choi Eun Seo.
Where are you going?
You are still on the clock.
Have you moved into
staff accommodations, yet?
That is why I am going home now
to pick up my stuff.
Be careful about what you do.
Because of people like you who think
everything is so fancy at a hotel,
all hardworking hotel staff gets blamed.
Please take it back.
I have not done anything to get blamed.
How dare you look straight into my eyes!
How shameless you are.
Haven't you done anything to get blamed?
People saw you pouring water
on the guest at the restaurant.
Are you dating at work?
Watch your behavior.
If I hear about such a thing again,
I will do everything to fire you.
You just try to be an overnight princess.
She is still young.
She's not that young, Mom.
You bastard.
- Why are you doing this to me?
- You...
President Kim,
why don't we set a date now?
No, it's fine.
Your sister doesn't seem to be home today,
so I will come again later.
Take this back, please.
No.
Please take them.
It is from my fishing boat.
I will come by later.
You, go away.
All right.
President Kim.
Why do you have to live
in staff accommodations?
I can come home once a week.
Mom, eat it.
President Kim...
brought fish again today.
I hate that he wants you, but...
he bailed out your brother several times
from being locked up.
Even this store...
No, never mind.
I am losing my mind.
I am sorry, mom.
But, please let me stay with you
a little longer.
If I work as I am doing now,
I will get my savings next year.
Then we will pay off the debt,
and then change our address legally.
Mom,
please let me live with you
a little longer.
I'm sorry.
If I knew this would happen,
I should've sent you away then.
Mom.
Jun Seo.
What do you think?
Do you think you like it here?
Yes, I like it a lot.
My classes in Seoul were done last week.
Should I move right away?
I would like that.
The duty of leaving this place empty...
and going back home
to please Mom bothers me.
Have you discussed things
with Yu Mi, though?
I have.
If I stay here, she can come here often.
That would be good for her health.
Right, you said she is not well.
By the way, are you going somewhere?
Yes, there is an interesting place,
so I will take some pictures.
You should come with me.
Are you taking pictures of squid?
What are you doing?
I am taking photos of the village
through this gap.
I see.
You keep taking your pictures.
I will go over there to look around.
All right.
Ji Hwan.
Aren't there any good ones?
I've got a good one. Where is it?
Yes, I have it here.
Who is it?
You haven't left for Seoul, yet.
What are you doing here
early in the morning?
Can I stay here for a couple of days?
- It is the key.
- Yes.
Here is your cell phone.
You can ask the front desk
to charge your cell phone.
What is going on, anyway?
I think I might see someone I know.
Did you see someone you know? Who?
Well,
I'll tell you later.
I'll tell you when I find her.
You have many secrets these days.
All right.
I'll see you when I get back from Seoul.
It'll take two or three days.
Until then, use whatever you want.
And...
you can't get close to my room attendant.
I know I don't need to warn you,
cause you are such a gentleman.
What about your room attendant?
Is it a woman?
Did you get back to your tricks here?
Yes, just playing around.
Hey, I don't think that's true.
Give me your cell phone.
What is she like?
Just wait here.
I'm just playing around.
I told you
I was going to my parents in Seoul.
I am on my way.
It's my friend's cell phone. Charge it.
My friend will stay in my room
for a couple of days.
What do you think about this watch?
Do you like it?
I will put on this instead.
Someone gave it to me
and I like it more than mine.
It has a stopwatch.
Look, you can see the date, too.
Do you want to see it? Look.
It has a light on.
I am sorry about earlier.
See you later.
- Sorry for keeping you waiting.
- That's all right.
Let's go.
- Hello.
- Yes, hi.
Is the number 0215?
It is fully charged.
I was told you were going to stay
for a couple of days.
I put your sleepwear in the closet
since there was no luggage.
You received several messages.
Jun Seo, it is me.
I wonder why you haven't called me.
I got your message.
Whom are you looking for?
Could you call me back to tell me more?
If you need anything,
my pager number is 012-323-0215.
The number is 0215.
It is the same number as mine.
Thank you so much, Ji Hwan.
But still.
She is an acquaintance of mine.
Yes.
Hello?
Ji Hwan, you are breaking up.
My phone is out of battery.
Hello.
Ji Hwan, I will call you back later.
Yes,
Is this the guest in the villa?
Did you page me?
Yes, I...
Hello?
I would like to charge my cell phone.
Of course, you can ask at the front desk.
Okay, thanks.
- I...
- So...
What brought you here?
Excuse me.
I am here to look for someone.
Have you found the person?
I am still looking for the person.
To charge your cell phone,
could you come to the front desk now?
I will be waiting for you.
Okay, I will come now.
It won't take long.
Hello?
Yes, this is he.
What?
Okay.
I am sorry. Please go to the airport.
Is she all right?
Is she okay?
What is going on?
She barely ate anything
because you were not coming back.
Now, look at her.
I am sorry.
Hello?
I am sorry. I did not know you came back.
Don't leave.
It is great that you came.
I was going to call you.
Do you need something?
Don't be too formal.
You are pretty.
It is interesting.
Is there something wrong with my vision?
What are you doing?
What am I doing?
Do you mean why am I drinking?
I...
Because...
You do not need to tell me
if it is something personal.
Excuse me.
I'm celebrating a wedding.
My mother in Japan got married again.
Is this the third time or the fourth?
If I count Dad,
this would be the fifth wedding.
You said you were going
to your mother's birthday dinner.
Did I?
I have two mothers.
One is my biological mother, who left me.
The other is the mother of my brothers
who totally ignore me.
Our madam.
Why am I telling you all this?
What are you?
Who are you?
All right.
I know why.
I am really interested in you.
You have something against me
since I told you all my secrets.
I am sorry. Excuse me.
Will you be my girlfriend?
Go out with me.
I will behave. I will try.
I will do anything for you.
Excuse me.
Stop there. Stop.
Hello.
Hello, is there anyone who paged me?
I did. It is the friend of Han Tae Seok.
I see. I wonder who it was.
I am sorry that I made you wait.
I am truly sorry. I had something urgent.
I am in Seoul now.
My friend...
My friend got sick, so...
I see.
It happens. Don't worry about it.
I actually...
I knew who paged me.
But I got annoyed a little.
So, I ignored it.
I waited quite a long time.
So, I even stopped by your room
minutes ago.
I remember your cell phone number.
You have the same last digits as mine,
so I memorized it.
Your number is 0215.
It is the date of a birthday.
For me too, it is a birthday.
Anyway, I'm sorry for making you wait.
It is all right.
I am glad you are okay,
and not in an accident or something.
Are you all right? You do not sound...
I am fine.
It's because of the rain.
The connection is not that good, right?
You must have returned without meeting
the person you were looking for.
Yes.
I think I have been mistaken.
Because I missed her so much.
I miss her so much that
I would mistake someone for her.
I see.
It was someone you missed that much.
Okay, then.
Hello.
Whose birthday is it?
What?
I meant your pager number.
It is my brother's birthday.
Whose birthday is it?
It is my birthday.
Okay.
All right.
Please visit our villa again, sir.
I will.
What should I do?
Yu Mi, you sit still just like a painting.
Am I not helpful?
I will organize paintings, then.
The painting organizes paintings.
Will it be all right to organize them
the way I like, Jun Seo?
Sure.
Is it far from here, this beach?
No, it's not. It's close.
Do you want to go there later?
You should draw me.
Come in.
Did you ask for me, sir?
Yes.
What happened to Choi Eun Seo?
Yes, sir.
Choi Eun Seo quit
because of an absurd guest.
She is absent without notice.
She is probably on a blind date
with a middle-aged man.
A middle-aged man?
She is being sold off.
If you do not need anything,
can I leave before getting fired?
Wait.
Be nice to him.
It's good that mom isn't home.
If she had been here...
I'm sick of that.
Hello, President Kim.
You are here.
Please get in the car.
Get in the car, now.
- You get in first, sir.
- All right, then.
President Kim.
I apologize.
You missed work without notice,
and you're on a blind date
with that old man.
Who made this happen?
I don't want to argue with you.
Acts of arguing and blaming you hurt me,
and I hate that.
I have listened to you
complaining about your life,
so now it's your turn.
I...
My family was deeply in debt
and ran away so many times.
And every time we ran away,
we owed money again.
My brother is a gangster.
He hurt his hand from fighting,
so he can't work anymore.
After he got injured, my mom...
lost the will to live.
So we make ends meet with my payroll.
But I quit my job now,
so what am I supposed to do?
That old man likes me.
He would buy me if I agreed to it.
That is enough. I should be grateful.
Right?
Aren't I right?
How much are you?
How much are you worth? I will buy you.
I will pay you more.
This beach,
this place is more than anything for me
with precious memories.
I'm so sad to be here with someone
like you, even for a minute.
I don't want to see you ever again.